easyformulaforsuccess.com 2011-05-01

# The Underdog Wealth System

EasyFormulaForSuccess.com takes your privacy seriously, and consequently, we have adopted the following Privacy Policy. 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy applies to the personal information that EasyFormulaForSuccess.com receives from you and thereafter stores in the company's database, including but not limited to information relating to your past use of EasyFormulaForSuccess.com products and services. "Personal information" is information about you such as your name, email address and such other similar information that is received from you by EasyFormulaForSuccess.com. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of individuals or companies that EasyFormulaForSuccess.com does not own or control or to individuals or other business entities that EasyFormulaForSuccess.com does not employ and manage. Although EasyFormulaForSuccess.com requires EasyFormulaForSuccess.com Affiliates and Publishers to adhere to Good Business Practices as a condition of their doing business with EasyFormulaForSuccess.com, EasyFormulaForSuccess.com does not own or control such Affiliates and Publishers, and as such, EasyFormulaForSuccess.com is not responsible for the information use and/or information gathering practices of any Affiliate or Publisher. Affiliates and Publishers are not employees or agents of EasyFormulaForSuccess.com, and the Internet User should understand that Affiliates and Publishers may collect personal information from or about Internet Users in manners and/or for purposes that are not consistent with the EasyFormulaForSuccess.com Privacy Policy. The collection, use, and disclosure of information by Affiliates and Publishers are subject to their own respective privacy policies, which may materially differ both in form and substance from the EasyFormulaForSuccess.com Privacy Policy. 

**Information Collection and Use**

EasyFormulaForSuccess.com collects personal information when you register or join with EasyFormulaForSuccess.com, when you use EasyFormulaForSuccess.com products or services, when you visit EasyFormulaForSuccess.com pages or the pages of certain EasyFormulaForSuccess.com advertisers, affiliates or publishers, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. EasyFormulaForSuccess.com may also combine information about you that we have with information that we obtain from advertisers or other companies. 

When you register or join, we ask for information such as your name, and email address. Once you register or join with EasyFormulaForSuccess.com and sign into our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

EasyFormulaForSuccess.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, EasyFormulaForSuccess.com cookie information, and the page you request. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by an Internet User's browser on the Internet User's hard drive. 

EasyFormulaForSuccess.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our customer services, contact you, conduct research, and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

EasyFormulaForSuccess.com does not rent, sell, or share personal identifying information about you with nonaffiliated individuals or companies except 1) where it is necessary to provide the information to acquire the products or services that you've requested and where we have your permission to do so; or 2) under the following circumstances: (a) we provide the information to nonaffiliated individuals or companies under confidentiality agreements for the purpose of allowing them to use your personal information to help EasyFormulaForSuccess.com communicate with you about offers from EasyFormulaForSuccess.com and/or our marketing partners, however, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information or to use this information for any purpose not consistent with the limited use identified in the foregoing sentence; or 3) we also share your personal identifying information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, and/or to establish and/or exercise our legal rights and/or to defend against legal claims, and we will also share your information at such times and under such circumstances that we determine, in our sole discretion, that it is necessary to share the information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the EasyFormulaForSuccess.com Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law; and 4) we will transfer information about you if EasyFormulaForSuccess.com is acquired by or merged with another company, and in this event, EasyFormulaForSuccess.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Additionally, EasyFormulaForSuccess.com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet their targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. EasyFormulaForSuccess.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. EasyFormulaForSuccess.com advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

**Cookies**

EasyFormulaForSuccess.com may set and access EasyFormulaForSuccess.com cookies on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to EasyFormulaForSuccess.com's cookies. EasyFormulaForSuccess.com uses web beacons to access EasyFormulaForSuccess.com cookies inside and outside of our network of web sites and in connection with EasyFormulaForSuccess.com products and services. 

EasyFormulaForSuccess.com may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our site, and it may also allow the companies that show advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their own cookies on your computer. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. These cookies are set and subsequently accessed on an Internet User™s computer after the user interacts with, views, or clicks on a targeted ad. If you do not wish to have other companies™ cookies set on your computer, do not interact with, view or click on the targeted ads. These other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not the Dentalplans.com Privacy Policy, and as such, their privacy policy may materially differ in both form and substance from the EasyFormulaForSuccess.com Privacy Policy. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to the personal information about you within our company to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information in order to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. Your EasyFormulaForSuccess.com Account Information is password-protected. In certain areas EasyFormulaForSuccess.com uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

EasyFormulaForSuccess.com may from time to time update this policy. We will notify you about any significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending you a notice to the primary email address specified in your EasyFormulaForSuccess.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

EasyFormulaForSuccess.com wants you to enjoy all of the savings discounts that are available to you as a member of EasyFormulaForSuccess.com. However, just as importantly, we want you to be assured that the information that you entrust to us stays private and confidential. 

Thank you for coming to our web site. We hope to have the honor of serving you as a member of EasyFormulaForSuccess.com for many years to come. Please also refer to Your Security about other privacy and security issues you may be interested in.
